export const quiz = {
    topic: 'Safer Internet',
    level: 'Medium',
    totalQuestions: 20,
    perQuestionScore: 10,
    questions: [
        {
            question:
                "C'est quoi l'inernet ?",
            choices: ['un outil de comminucation', 'le web', 'réseaux mondiaux interconnectés', 'Tout ce qui précède'],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'réseaux mondiaux interconnectés',
        }, {
            question:
                "What is the cybersecurity",
            choices: ['defending againnst viruses', 'attacking other systems', 'protecting servers,computers... against cyberattacks', 'Rien'],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'protecting servers,computers... against cyberattacks',
        }, {
            question:
                "When the virus of love released",
            choices: ['1900', '2001', '2007', '1999'],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: '1999',
        }, {
            question:
                "What is the average number of cyberattacks happening per day",
 

            choices: ['2220', '2000', '30000', '4223'],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: '2220',
        }, {
            question:
                "كيف احمي نفسي في الانترنت ؟",
            choices: ['استخدام متصفح قوي', 'استخدام شبكات اتصال عامة', 'تحميل برامج من مصادر مشبوهة', 'عمل تحذيثات للجهاز'],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'عمل تحذيثات للجهاز',
        }, {
            question:
                "What is a virus ?",
            choices: ['prorgrammed application', 'type of malicious code or program', 'decoded passwords', 'application of malware'],

            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'type of malicious code or program',
        }, {
            question:
                "Qu'est-ce qu'un firewall ?",
            choices: ['matériel et logiciel qui sépare un réseau local', 'logiciel qui sépare un réseau local', 'matériel qui sépare un réseau local', 'Un application de securité'],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'matériel et logiciel qui sépare un réseau local',
        }, {
            question:
                "Comment puis-je connaître un site Web frauduleux ??",
            choices: ["en utilisant l'url du site", "à l'aide d'une application de sécurité", 'Assurez-vous que le domaine correspond au certificat SSL', 'Tout ce qui précède'],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'Tout ce qui précède',
        }, {
            question:
                "HTTP signifie",
            choices: ['hyper text transfer protocol', 'hypertet transmission protocol', 'high transfer transport protocol', 'hyper transfer text protocol'],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'hyper text transfer protocol',
        }, {
            question:
                "We access the World Wide Web using",
            choices: ['Browsers', 'Instant messaging applications', 'High bandwidth', 'Search engine'],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'Browsers',
        }, {
            question:
                "_____جهازان كمبيوتر أو أكثر متصلان ببعضهما البعض يتشاركان المعلومات من ",
            choices: ['شبكة', 'جهاز التوجيه', 'الخادم', 'نفق'],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'شبكة',
        }, {
            question:
                "What is the full form of WWW?",
            choices: ['World Wide Web', 'World With Web', 'Work Wide Web', 'World Wide Wet'],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'World Wide Web',
        }, {
            question:
                "The design of the network is called the network:",
            choices: ['architecture', 'server', 'transmission', 'type'],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'architecture',
        }, {
            question:
                "Programs such as Mozila Firefox that serve as navigable windows onto the Web are called ___",
            choices: ['Hypertext', 'Networks', 'Internet', 'Web browsers'],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'Web browsers',
        }, {
            question:
                "Le serveur sur Internet est également connu sous le nom de :",
            choices: ['Répétitrice', 'hôtesse', 'passerelle', 'Porte ET'],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'hôtesse',
        }, {
            question:
                "Le site Web est une collection de:",
            choices: ['HTML documents', 'Fichiers graphiques', 'Fichiers audio et vidéo', 'Tout ce qui précède'],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'Tout ce qui précède',
        }, {
            question:
                "Which of the following is not a network ?",
            choices: ['Local Area Network', 'Wide Area Network', 'Optical Fibre', 'All are networks'],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'Optical Fibre',
        }, {
            question:
                "Sending email contain a suspicious application is_____",
            choices: ['Phishing', 'Scamming', 'CyberCrime', 'All of the above'],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'All of the above',
        }, {
            question:
                "DSL est un exemple de connexion a(n)",
            choices: ['network', 'wireless', 'slow', 'broadband'],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'broadband',
        }, {
            question:
                "Qu'est-ce que le domaine de premier niveau de code de pays Internet (ccTLD) pour les îles de Tuvalu ?",
            choices: ['.ta', '.tu', '.tl', '.tv'],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: '.tv',
        }
    ],
}